<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Landon Ferguson</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Landon Ferguson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data-FX</title>
      <link>/projects/data-fx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/data-fx/</guid>
      <description>Data-FX is a blender3d addon that adds the ability to load and visualize data using various different charts.
It started as a fun way to learn more about the Python language, but ended up being a fun ongoing side-project that I update regularly.
   --  View the code  View all posts tagged with &#34;Data-FX&#34;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unity Fluid</title>
      <link>/projects/unity-fluid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 04:58:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/unity-fluid/</guid>
      <description>Position Based Dynamics This fluid sim runs entirely on the GPU using Unity Compute Shaders, implementing the method from this research paper. The current implementation uses a Bitonic sort for spatial hashing, though other parallel sorting algorithms could potentially offer better performance.
 GPU Handles Collisions Since the fluid system runs entirely on the GPU, we have to draw physical objects as a set of particles on the GPU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bartender Bot</title>
      <link>/projects/bartender-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 02:49:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/bartender-bot/</guid>
      <description>Overview The bar uses 6 servo-controlled valves to dispense the drinks, and 4 air pumps connected to a relay board to dispense the mixers.
Back-End For this project, I used Nodejs and the SocketIO library for realtime client &amp;gt; server communication.
The pi emits the local webserver you can connect to from any device on the network, including a windows tablet attatched to the bar.
The client then sends the drink selection data back to the server, and the server passes that data to a python script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I-Hear-Them</title>
      <link>/projects/i-hear-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 04:58:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/i-hear-them/</guid>
      <description>I-Hear-Them is an in-browser 3D first-person horror game made with ThreeJS with the help of some custom built shaders.
   --  Play a demo  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
